<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2014 Urs Fleisch <ufleisch_at_users.sourceforge.net> -->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kid3.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">كِد3</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKid3xx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Kid3</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Kid3</name>
  <summary>Edit audio file metadata</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">حرّر البيانات الوصفيّة للملفات الصوتية</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Edita les metadades dels fitxers d'àudio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Edita les metadades dels fitxers d'àudio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Upravujte metadata souboru hudby</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Redigér metadata for lydfiler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Metadaten von Audio-Dateien bearbeiten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Επεξεργασία μεταδεδομένων αρχείου ήχου </summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Edit audio file metadata</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Redaktu aŭdio-dosierajn metadatenojn</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Edición de metadatos de archivos de sonido</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Helifailide metaandmete muutmine</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Editatu audio fitxategietako metadatuak</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Muokkaa äänitiedostojen metatietoja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Éditer les métadonnées de fichiers audio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Edit metadata file audio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="is">Breyta lýsigögnum í hljóðskrám</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Modifica i metadati dei file audio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">აუდიო ფაილის მეტამონაცემების ჩასწორება</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">오디오 파일 메타데이터 편집</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Metagegevens van audiobestanden bewerken</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Rediger metadata for lydfiler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Edytuj metadane pliku dźwiękowego</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Editar os meta-dados dos ficheiros de áudio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Edita metadados de arquivos de áudio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Редактирование метаданных звуковых файлов</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Upraviť metadáta zvukového súboru</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Urejanje metapodatkov zvočne datoteke</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Redigera metadata i ljudfiler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Ses dosyası üstverisini düzenleyin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Редагування метаданих звукових файлів</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxEdit audio file metadataxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">编辑音频文件元数据</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">編輯音訊檔案中繼資料</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      With Kid3, an audio tag editor, you can edit tags in MP3, Ogg/Vorbis,
      DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack,
      WMA, WAV, AIFF and tracker files.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">باستخدام كِد3 يمكنك تحرير وسوم في ملفات MP3 و Ogg/Vorbis و DSF و FLAC و Opus و MPCو APE و MP4/AAC و  MP2و  Speexو TrueAudio و WavPack و WMA و WAV و .AIFF</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Amb el Kid3, un editor per a les etiquetes de l'àudio, podreu editar les etiquetes als fitxers MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF i del seguidor de peces.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Amb Kid3, un editor per a les etiquetes de l'àudio, podreu editar les etiquetes en els fitxers MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF i del seguidor de peces.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Pomocí Kid3, editoru značek hudby, můžete upravovat značky v MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF a dalších souborech.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Kid3 er en lydmærke-editor, hvormed du kan redigere mærker i MP3-, Ogg/Vorbis-, DSF-, FLAC-, Opus-, MPC-, APE-, MP4/AAC-, MP2-, Speex-, TrueAudio-, WavPack-, WMA-, WAV-, AIFF- og tracker-filer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Mit Kid3, einem Editor für Audio-Metadaten, können Sie Tags in MP3-, Ogg/Vorbis-, DSF-, FLAC-, Opus-, MPC-, APE-, MP4/AAC-, MP2-, Speex-, TrueAudio-, WavPack-, WMA-, WAV-, AIFF- und und Tracker-Dateien bearbeiten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Με το Kid3, έναν επεξεργαστή ετικετών ήχου, μπορείτε να επεξεργαστείτε ετικέτες σε MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF και σε αρχεία ιχνηλάτησης.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">With Kid3, an audio tag editor, you can edit tags in MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF and tracker files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Kun Kid3, aŭd-etikedredaktilo, vi povas redakti etikedojn en MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF kaj tracker-dosieroj.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Con Kid3, un editor de etiquetas de sonido, puede editar etiquetas en MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF y archivos tracker.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Helifailide siltide redaktor Kid3 võimaldab muuta MP3-, Ogg/Vorbise, DSF-, FLAC-, Opuse, MPC-, APE-, MP4/AAC-, MP2-, Speex-, TrueAudio-, WavPack-, WMA-, WAV-, AIFF- ja tracker-failide silte.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Kid3-rekin, audio etiketa editorea izaki, MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF eta tracker fitxategien etiketak editatu ditzakezu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Kid3-äänitunnistemuokkaimella voi muokata tunnisteita MP3-, Ogg/Vorbis-, DSF-, FLAC-, Opus-, MPC-, APE-, MP4/AAC-, MP2-, Speex-, TrueAudio-, WavPack-, WMA-, WAV-, AIFF- ja Tracker-tiedostoissa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Avec Kid3, un éditeur d'étiquettes de fichiers audio, vous pouvez éditer les étiquettes dans les fichiers de type MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP3/AAC, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Dengan Kid3, sebuah pengedit tag audio, kamu bisa mengedit tag-tag di dalam file-file MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF dan sebagai pelacak.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Með Kid3 geturðu merkt ýmis lýsigögn inn í hljóðskrár, meðal annars í MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF og tracker-rakningarskrár.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Con Kid3, un editor di tag audio, puoi modificare i tag nei file MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF e nei tracker.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">오디오 태그 편집기 Kid3을 사용하여 MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF, 트래커 파일의 태그를 편집할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Met Kid3, een audiotagbewerker, kunt u tags in MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF en trackerbestanden bewerken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Med Kid3 kan du redigera metadata for lydfiler i formata MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF og tracket.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Dzięki Kid3, edytorowi znaczników plików dźwiękowych, możesz edytować znaczniki w plikach MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF oraz plikach serwerów śledzących.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Com o Kid3, um editor de marcas de áudio, poderá editar as marcas dos ficheiros MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF e Tracker.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Com o Kid3, um editor de etiquetas de áudio, você pode editar as etiquetas no MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF e arquivos tracker.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Kid3, редактор аудиотегов, позволяет редактировать теги файлов в формате MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF и файлов трекеров.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">S editorom zvukových značiek Kid3 môžete upravovať značky v súboroch MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF a sledovacie súbory.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Z urejevalnikom zvočnih oznak Kid3, lahko urejate oznake v datoteke MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF in datoteke sledilcev.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Med Kid3, en editor för ljudtaggar, kan du redigera taggar i MP3-, Ogg/Vorbis-, DSF-, FLAC-, Opus-, MPC-, APE-, MP4/AAC-, MP2-, Speex-, TrueAudio-, WavPack-, WMA-, WAV-, AIFF- och tracker-filer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Kid3 ses etiketi düzenleyicisi ile MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF ve izleyici dosyalardaki etiketleri düzenleyebilirsiniz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">За допомогою Kid3, редактора міток звукових файлів, ви можете редагувати мітки у файлах MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF та tracker.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxWith Kid3, an audio tag editor, you can edit tags in MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIFF and tracker files.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">Kid3 是一个音频标签编辑器，您可以使用它编辑 MP3, Ogg/Vorbis, DSF, FLAC, Opus, MPC, APE, MP4/AAC, MP2, Speex, TrueAudio, WavPack, WMA, WAV, AIF 和 Tracker 文件。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">使用 Kid3 這個音訊標籤編輯器，即可編輯 MP3、Ogg/Vorbis、DSF、FLAC、Opus、MPC、APE、MP4/AAC、MP2、Speex、TrueAudio、WavPack、WMA、WAV、AIFF 和 tracker 檔案中的標籤。</p>
    <p>
      All frames in the ID3 tags of MP3 files can be edited, and it is
      possible to convert between ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 and ID3v2.4. Synchronized
      lyrics can be edited, imported and exported to LRC Karaoke files.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يمكن تحرير جميع وسوم ID3 لملفات MP3 ، ومن الممكن تحويلها بين ID3v1.1 و ID3v2.3 و ID3v2.4. يمكن تحرير كلمات الأغاني المتزامنة واستيرادها وتصديرها إلى ملفات LRC Karaoke.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Es poden editar tots els marcs en les etiquetes ID3 dels fitxers MP3, i és possible convertir-les entre l'ID3 versió 1.1, 2.3 i 2.4. La lletra sincronitzada es pot editar, importar i exportar a fitxers de Karaoke en LRC.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Es poden editar tots els marcs en les etiquetes ID3 dels fitxers MP3, i és possible convertir-les entre l'ID3 versió 1.1, 2.3 i 2.4. La lletra sincronitzada es pot editar, importar i exportar a fitxers de Karaoke en LRC.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Alle rammer i ID3-mærkerne for MP3-filer kan redigeres, og det er muligt at konvertere mellem ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 og ID3v2.4. Synkroniserede sangtekster kan redigeres, importeres og eksporteres til LRC karaoke-filer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Alle Elemente in den ID3-Tags von MP3-Dateien können bearbeitet und zwischen ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 und ID3v2.4 umgewandelt werden. Synchronisierte Liedtexte können bearbeitet, importiert und in LRC-Karaoke-Dateien exportiert werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Όλα τα καρέ στις ID3 ετικέτες των MP3 αρχείων μπορούν να γίνουν αντικείμενο επεξεργασίας και είναι εφικτή η μετατροπή ανάμεσα σε ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 και ID3v2.4. Μπορεί να γίνει επεξεργασία, εισαγωγή και εξαγωγή συγχρονισμένων στίχων σε LRC καραόκε αρχεία.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">All frames in the ID3 tags of MP3 files can be edited, and it is possible to convert between ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 and ID3v2.4. Synchronised lyrics can be edited, imported and exported to LRC Karaoke files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Ĉiuj kadroj en la ID3-etikedoj de MP3-dosieroj estas redakteblaj, kaj eblas konverti inter ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 kaj ID3v2.4. Sinkronigitaj kantotekstoj povas esti redaktitaj, importitaj kaj eksportitaj al LRC Karaoke-dosieroj.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Se pueden editar todas las estructuras de etiquetas ID3 de los archivos MP3. Es posible convertir entre ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 e ID3v2.4. Se pueden editar las letras de las canciones sincronizadas, además de importarlas y exportarlas a archivos de karaoke LRC.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Kõiki MP3-faili ID3 siltide kaadreid saab muuta ning võimalik on teisendamine ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 ja ID3v2.4 vahel. Sünkroonitud laulusõnu saab muuta, importida ja eksportida LRC Karaoke failina.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">ID3 etiketetako bilbe guztiak editatu daitezke, eta ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 eta ID3v2.4 arteko bihurketa egin daiteke. Sinkronizatutako hitzak editatu, inportatu eta LRC Karaoke fitxategietara esportatu daitezke.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Kaikkia MP3-tiedostojen ID3-tunnistekenttiä voi muokata, ja muunnos ID3v1.1:n, ID3v2.3:n ja ID3v2.4:n välillä on mahdollista. Synkronoituja sanoituksia voi muokata, tuoda ja viedä LRC Karaoke -tiedostoiksi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Tous les champs dans les étiquettes ID3 des fichiers MP3 peuvent être édités, et il est possible de convertir entre les formats ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 et ID3v2.4. Les paroles synchronisées peuvent être éditées, importées et exportées au format LRC (pour karaoké).</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Semua bingkai dalam tag ID3 pada file MP3 bisa diedit, dan dimungkinkan untuk konversi antara ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 dan ID3v2.4. Lirik yang disinkronkan bisa diedit, diimpor dan diekspor ke file Karaoke LRC.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Öllum römmum í ID3-merkjum MP3-skráa má breyta, auk þess að mögulegt er að umbreyta á milli ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 og ID3v2.4 merkja. Hægt er að vinna með samstillta lagatexta; breyta, flytja inn og flytja út í LRC-karíókískrár.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Possono essere modificati tutti i frame dei tag ID3 dei file MP3, ed è possibile convertire i tag tra ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 e ID3v2.4. I testi sincronizzati possono essere modificati, importati ed esportati in file LRC Karaoke.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">MP3 파일의 ID3 태그의 모든 프레임을 편집할 수 있으며, ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3, ID3v2.4 사이를 변환할 수 있습니다. 실시간 가사를 편집 및 가져올 수 있으며 LRC 형식 노래방 파일로 내보낼 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Alle frames in de ID3-tags van MP3 bestanden kunnen bewerkt worden en het is mogelijk te converteren tussen ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 en ID3v2.4 te converteren. Gesynchroniseerde liedteksten kunnen bewerkt, geïmporteerd en geëxporteerd worden naar LRC Karaoke bestanden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Du kan redigera alle metadata­rammene i ID3-merke­lappane i MP3-filer, og du kan konvertera mellom ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 og ID3v2.4. Synkroniserte songtekstar kan redigerast, importerast og eksporterast til LRC-karaokefiler.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Można edytować wszystkie klatki w znacznikach ID3 plików MP3. Możliwe jest przekształcanie pomiędzy ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 oraz ID3v2.4. Można edytować zsynchronizowane słowa, zaimportowane i wyeksportowane pliki do LRC Karaoke.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Todos os dados nas marcas ID3 dos ficheiros MP3 poderão ser editados, sendo possível converter entre os formatos ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 e ID3v2.4. Poderá editar de forma sincronizada as letras musicais, podendo importar e exportar para ficheiros de Karaoke LRC.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Todos os quadros nas etiquetas ID3 de arquivos MP3 podem ser editados e é possível converter entre ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 e ID3v2.4. Letras sincronizadas podem ser editadas, importadas e exportadas para arquivos de karaokê LRC.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Возможно редактировать все фреймы в тегах ID3 MP3-файлов, а также осуществлять преобразование данных между тегами ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 и ID3v2.4. Синхронизированные тексты песен возможно редактировать, импортировать и экспортировать в файлы караоке LRC.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Všetky polia v ID3 tagoch MP3 súborov je možné editovať a je možné prevádzať medzi ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 a ID3v2.4. Synchronizované texty je možné editovať, importovať a exportovať do súborov LRC Karaoke.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Vsi okviri v ID3 oznakah MP3 datotek se lahko urejajo in jih je možno pretvoriti med ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 in ID3v2.4. Sinhronizirana besedila se lahko urejajo, uvažajo in izvažajo v datoteke LRC Karaoke.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Alla ramer i ID3-taggarna för MP3-filer kan redigeras, och det är möjligt att konvertera mellan ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 och ID3v2.4. Synkroniserade sångtexter kan redigeras, importeras och exporteras till LRC Karaoke-filer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">MP3 dosyalarındaki ID3 etiketlerinin tüm kareleri düzenlenebilir ve ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 and ID3v2.4 arasında dönüştürülebilir. Uyuşturulan şarkı sözleri düzenlenebilir ve LRC Karaoke dosyası olarak içe/dışa aktarılabilir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Передбачено можливість редагувати усі кадри у мітках ID3 файлів MP3. Передбачено можливість перетворення між форматами ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 і ID3v2.4. Синхронізовані тексти пісень можна редагувати, імпортувати та експортувати до файлів караоке LRC.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxAll frames in the ID3 tags of MP3 files can be edited, and it is possible to convert between ID3v1.1, ID3v2.3 and ID3v2.4. Synchronized lyrics can be edited, imported and exported to LRC Karaoke files.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">可编辑 MP3 文件中 ID3 标签内的所有帧，并能在 ID3v1.1、ID3v2.3 和 ID3v2.4 转换。不仅能编辑同步歌词，还能导入或导出 LRC Karaoke 文件。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">MP3 檔案的 ID3 標籤中的所有音框都能夠編輯，也能夠在 ID3v1.1、ID3v2.3 及 ID3v2.4 之間轉換。提供對內嵌同步歌詞的編輯、匯入及輸出到卡拉 OK 用的 LRC 檔案的功能。</p>
    <p>
      The tags of multiple files can be set together. It is possible to
      generate tags from file names or the contents of other tag fields and to
      generate file names from tags and rename folders from tags. Automatic
      case conversion and string replacement help to keep tags consistent.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يمكن ضبط وسوم الملفات المتعددة معًا. ومن الممكن إنشاء وسوم من أسماء الملفات أو محتويات حقول الوسوم الأخرى وإنشاء أسماء الملفات من الوسوم وإعادة تسمية المجلدات من الوسوم. ويمكن تحويل الحالة الأحرف واستبدال النصوص بشكل آليا حتى تكون متسقة.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Es poden establir juntes les etiquetes de múltiples fitxers. És possible generar etiquetes a partir de noms de fitxer o el contingut d'altres camps d'etiqueta i generar noms de fitxer a partir d'etiquetes i canviar el nom de les carpetes a partir de les etiquetes. La conversió automàtica de majúscules i minúscules, i la substitució de cadenes ajuden a mantenir les etiquetes coherents.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Es poden establir juntes les etiquetes de múltiples fitxers. És possible generar etiquetes a partir de noms de fitxer o el contingut d'altres camps d'etiqueta i generar noms de fitxer a partir d'etiquetes i canviar el nom de les carpetes a partir de les etiquetes. La conversió automàtica de majúscules i minúscules, i la substitució de cadenes ajuden a mantindre les etiquetes coherents.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Mærker fra flere filer kan sættes sammen. Det er muligt at generere mærker ud fra filnavne eller indholdet af andre mærkefelter samt at generere filnavne fra mærker og omdøbe mapper ud fra mærker. Automatisk konvertering af versaler og erstatning af strenge hjælper med at holde mærkerne konsistente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Die Tags von mehreren Dateien können gemeinsam festgelegt werden. Es ist möglich, Tags aus Dateinamen oder dem Inhalt anderer Tag-Felder und Dateinamen aus Tags zu generieren und Ordner aus Tags umzubenennen. Automatische Groß-/Kleinschreibung und die Ersetzung von Zeichenfolgen helfen dabei, Tags einheitlich zu halten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Οι ετικέτες πολλών αρχείων μπορούν να ρυθμιστούν μαζί. Είναι δυνατή η παραγωγή ετικετών από ονόματα αρχείων ή από τα περιεχόμενα άλλων πεδίων ετικετών, η παραγωγή ονομάτων αρχείων από ετικέτες και η μετονομασία φακέλων από ετικέτες. Η αυτόματη μετατροπή μεταξύ κεφαλαίων και πεζών και η αντικατάσταση συμβολοσειρών βοηθούν στη διατήρηση των ετικετών σε συμφωνία.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">The tags of multiple files can be set together. It is possible to generate tags from file names or the contents of other tag fields and to generate file names from tags and rename folders from tags. Automatic case conversion and string replacement help to keep tags consistent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">La etikedoj de pluraj dosieroj povas esti agordita kune. Eblas generi etikedojn el dosiernomoj aŭ la enhavon de aliaj etikedkampoj kaj generi dosiernomojn el etikedoj kaj renomi dosierujojn el etikedoj. Aŭtomata uskla konvertiĝo kaj anstataŭigo de ŝnuroj helpas konservi etikedojn konsekvencaj.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Puede definir de forma conjunta las etiquetas de múltiples archivos. Es posible generar etiquetas a partir de los nombres de los archivos o del contenido de otras etiquetas y generar nombres de archivos a partir de etiquetas, así como cambiar los nombres de las carpetas a partir de etiquetas. La conversión automática a mayúsculas y la sustitución de texto ayudan a mantener etiquetas consistentes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Mitme faili silte saab kokku siduda. Silte on võimalik luua failinime või teiste siltide väljade põhjal ning siltide põhjal saab nii luua failinimesid kui ka muuta kataloogide nime. Siltide ühtlust aitavad tagada automaatne tähesuuruse teisendamine ja stringi asendamine.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Fitxategi askotako etiketak elkarrekin ezar daitezke. Fitxategi-izenetatik edo beste etiketa eremuetako edukietatik etiketak sor daitezke, baita etiketetatik fitxategi-izenak sortu eta karpetak berrizendatu ere. Letra larri/xehe bihurketa automatikoak eta kate ordezkapenak etiketak koherente mantentzen laguntzen dute.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Tunnisteet voi asettaa usealle tiedostolle yhtä aikaa. Tunnisteet voi kehittää tiedostonimistä tai muiden tunnistekenttien sisällöstä tai päinvastoin tuottaa tiedosto- ja kansionimet tunnisteista. Tunnisteiden yhtenäisenä pitämisen helpottamiseksi voi pien- ja suuraakkostusta muuttaa ja merkkijonoja korvata automaattisesti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Les étiquettes de plusieurs fichiers peuvent être mises ensemble. Il est aussi possible de générer les étiquettes à partir des noms des fichiers ou des contenus d'autres champs. Les noms des fichiers peuvent aussi être générés à partir des étiquettes et les dossiers peuvent être renommés à partir des étiquettes. La conversion de casse et le remplacement des chaînes automatiques permettent de conserver les étiquettes consistantes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Tag dari beberapa file bisa disatukan. Yang memungkinkan untuk membuat tag dari nama file atau konten kolom tag lainnya dan untuk menghasilkan nama file dari tag dan mengganti nama folder dari tag. Konversi otomatis dan penggantian string membantu menjaga konsistensi tag.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Hægt er að stilla lýsigagnamerki á mörgum skrám í einu. Útbúa má merki sjálfvirkt út frá skráaheitum eða innihaldi annarra merkja, eins er hægt að útbúa skráaheiti og endurnefna möppur út frá merkjum. Sjálfvirk umbreyting milli há-/lágstafa og útskipting í strengjum hjálpa síðan til við að halda samræmi á milli lýsigagnamerkja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Possono essere impostati assieme i tag di più file. È possibile generare tag dai nomi file o dal contenuto di altri campi tag, generare i nomi file dai tag e rinominare cartelle dai tag. La conversione tra maiuscole e minuscole e la sostituzione di stringhe aiutano a mantenere i tag coerenti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">파일 여러 개에 태그를 한 번에 설정할 수 있습니다. 파일 이름이나 다른 태그 필드의 내용에서 태그를 생성할 수 있으며, 태그를 기반으로 파일이나 폴더의 이름을 변경할 수 있습니다. 태그의 일관성을 유지하는 자동 대소문자 변환과 문자열 대체를 지원합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">De tags van meerdere bestanden kunnen samen ingesteld worden. Het is mogelijk tags te genereren uit bestandsnamen of de inhoud van andere tagvelden en bestandsnamen te genereren uit tags en mappen te hernoemen uit tags. Automatisch conversie van hoofd- kleine letter en vervangen van tekenreeksen helpen om tags consistent te houden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Du kan redigera metadata for fleire filer samtidig og generera metadata frå filnamn eller innhaldet i andre metadata­felt, eller generera fil- og mappe­namn frå metadataa. Du kan òg gjera automatiske endringar i bruken av stor/liten (for)bokstav og andre automatiske tekstutbytingar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Można na raz ustawić jeden znacznik dla wielu plików. Możliwe jest tworzenie znaczników z nazw plików lub treści innego znacznika lub tworzenie nazw plików ze znaczników oraz zmiana nazw katalogów ze znaczników. Zamiana wielkości liter oraz ciągów znaków pomaga w zachowaniu spójności w znacznikach.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Poderá definir em conjunto as marcas de vários ficheiros. É possível gerar marcas a partir dos nomes dos ficheiros ou do conteúdo de outros campos de marcas, assim como gerar nomes dos ficheiros a partir das marcas e mudar os nomes das pastas a partir das mesmas. A conversão automática de maiúsculas/minúsculas e a substituição de textos ajudam a manter as marcas consistentes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">As etiquetas de múltiplos arquivos pode ser definidas em conjunto. É possível gerar etiquetas a partir do nome do arquivo ou conteúdo de outros campos da etiqueta e gerar nomes de arquivos e renomear pastas a partir das etiquetas. A conversão automática de maiúsculas e substituição de texto ajudam a manter as etiquetas consistentes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Предусмотрена возможность установки тегов одновременно в несколько файлов. Возможно создавать теги из имён файлов или содержимого других полей тегов, а также создавать имена файлов из тегов и переименовывать каталоги на основе тегов. Автоматическое преобразование регистра и замена строк помогают поддерживать согласованность тегов.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Značky viacerých súborov je možné nastaviť naraz. Je možné generovať značky z názvov súborov alebo z obsahu iných polí značiek a generovať názvy súborov zo značiek a premenovať priečinky zo značiek. Automatická konverzia veľkých a malých písmen a nahradenie reťazca pomáhajú udržiavať konzistentnosť značiek.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Oznake več datotek je mogoče nastaviti skupaj. Možno je ustvariti oznake iz imen datotek ali vsebine drugih označenih polj in za ustvarjanje imen datotek iz oznak in preimenovanje map iz oznak. Samodejna pretvorba malih v velike črke in obratno in zamenjava nizov pomaga doslednosti in konsistentnosti oznak.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Taggar för flera filer kan ställas in samtidigt. Det är möjligt att generera taggar från filnamn eller innehållet i andra taggfält, och att generera filnamn från taggar och byta namn på kataloger från taggar. Automatisk skiftlägeskonvertering och strängersättning hjälper till att hålla taggar konsekventa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Birden çok dosyanın etiketi bir araya getirilebilir. Dosya adlarından, diğer etiket alanlarının içeriğinden etiket oluşturulabilir. Etiketlerden dosya adları oluşturmak olanaklıdır ve etiketlerden klasörler yeniden adlandırılabilir. Otomatik harf dönüşümü ve dizi değişimi etiketleri düzgün tutmaya yardımcı olur.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Передбачено можливість встановлювати мітки для цілих наборів файлів. Передбачено можливість створювати мітки на основі назв файлів або вмісту інших полів міток і створювати назви файлів на основі міток і перейменовувати теки на основі міток. Автоматичне перетворення регістру символів та заміна рядків допоможуть вам у підтриманні однорідності міток у вашій збірці.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThe tags of multiple files can be set together. It is possible to generate tags from file names or the contents of other tag fields and to generate file names from tags and rename folders from tags. Automatic case conversion and string replacement help to keep tags consistent.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">一同设置多个文件的标签。可从文件名或其他标签字段中的内容生成标签、根据标签生成文件名或根据标签重命名文件夹。并能通过自动转换大小写和字符串替换保持标签一致性。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">可以同時設定多個檔案的標籤。可以從檔案名稱或其他標籤欄位的內容產生新的標籤內容，也可以從標籤產生新的檔案名稱或是資料夾名稱。提供自動大小寫變換與字串取代，幫助標籤維持一致性。</p>
    <p>
      Album data can be imported from gnudb.org, MusicBrainz,
      Discogs, Amazon; automatic batch import is available for multiple
      folders. It is also possible to export data and generate play lists.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يمكن استيراد بيانات الألبوم من gnudb.org و MusicBrainz و Discogs و Amazon ؛ تتوفر استيراد بالدُفعات التلقائية لمجلدات متعددة. من الممكن أيضًا تصدير البيانات وإنشاء قوائم التشغيل.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Les dades de l'àlbum es poden importar des de gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon. Hi ha disponible la importació automàtica per lots per a múltiples carpetes. També és possible exportar dades i generar llistes de reproducció.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Les dades de l'àlbum es poden importar des de gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon. Hi ha disponible la importació automàtica per lots per a múltiples carpetes. També és possible exportar dades i generar llistes de reproducció.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Albumdaten können von gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon importiert werden. Ein automatischer Stapelverarbeitungsmodus ist für mehrere Ordner verfügbar. Daten können exportiert und Wiedergabelisten können erstellt werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Δεδομένα για άλμπουμ μπορούν να εισαχθούν από τα gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon. Η αυτόματη εισαγωγή δέσμης είναι διαθέσιμη για πολλούς φακέλους. Είναι επίσης δυνατή η εξαγωγή δεδομένων και η δημιουργία λιστών αναπαραγωγής.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Album data can be imported from gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon; automatic batch import is available for multiple folders. It is also possible to export data and generate play lists.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Albumaj datumoj povas esti importitaj de gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon; aŭtomata grupa importo disponeblas por pluraj dosierujoj. Ankaŭ eblas eksporti datumojn kaj generi ludlistojn.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Puede importar datos de álbumes de gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs y Amazon. Puede realizar importaciones automáticas por lotes para múltiples carpetas. También puede exportar datos y generar listas de reproducción.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Albumi andmeid saab importida gnudb.org-ist, MusicBrainzist, Discogsist ja Amazonist. Automaatne hulgiimport võimaldab täita mitut kataloogi korraga. Samuti saab andmeid eksportida ja luua esitusloendeid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Albumen datuak inportatu daitezke ondokoetatik, gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon; sortakako inportatze automatikoa erabilgarri dago karpeta anizkoitzetarako. Gainera, datuak esportatu eta jotze-zerrendak sor daitezke.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Albumin tiedot voi tuoda gnudb.orgista, MusicBrainzistä, Discogsista ja Amazonista. Useamman kansion automaattinen eräajotuonti on mahdollista. Tiedot voi myös viedä ja luoda soittolistan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Les données des albums peuvent être importées de gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs et Amazon. Une importation automatique sur plusieurs dossiers en même temps est disponible. Il est aussi possible d'exporter les données et de générer des listes de lecture.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Data album bisa diimpor dari gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon; impor batch otomatis telah tersedia untuk multipel folder. Yang juga memungkinkan untuk mengekspor data dan menghasilkan daftar playlist.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Hægt er að flytja inn upplýsingar um tónlist úr gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon; hægt er að nota magninnflutning fyrir margar möppur í einu. Einnig er hægt að flytja út gögn og útbúa spilunarlista.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">È possibile importare i dati dell'album da gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon; è disponibile l'importazione automatica in serie per più cartelle. È inoltre possibile esportare i dati e generare scalette.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon에서 앨범 데이터를 가져올 수 있습니다. 여러 폴더에서 자동으로 일괄적 가져오기를 수행할 수 있습니다. 데이터를 내보내고 재생 목록을 생성할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Albumgegevens kunnen geïmporteerd worden uit gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon; automatische bulkimport is beschikbaar voor meerdere mappen. Het is ook mogelijk gegevens te exporteren en afspeellijsten te genereren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Albumdata kan importerast frå gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs og Amazon, og for fleire album/mapper samtidig. Dei kan òg eksporterast til ulike format, for eksempel som spelelister.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Dane albumu można zaimportować z gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon; importowanie wsadowe jest możliwe dla wielu katalogów. Możliwe jest także eksportowanie danych i tworzenie list odtwarzania.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Os dados dos álbuns podem ser importados a partir do gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon; está disponível a importação automática em lote para várias pastas. Também é possível exportar os dados e gerar listas de reprodução.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Os dados de álbuns podem ser importados de gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon; a importação em lotes está disponível para múltiplas pastas. Também é possível exportar dados e gerar listas de reprodução.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Данные об альбомах возможно импортировать из gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon; доступна функция автоматического пакетного импорта для нескольких каталогов. Также возможно экспортировать данные и создавать списки воспроизведения.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Podatke o albumu lahko uvozite iz gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon; samodejni uvoz paketov je na voljo za več map. Možen je tudi izvoz podatkov in ustvarjanje seznamov predvajanja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Albumdata kan importeras från gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, eller Amazon. Automatisk import i bakgrunden är tillgänglig för flera kataloger. Det är också möjligt att exportera data och skapa spellistor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Albüm verisi gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon konumlarından içe aktarılabilir; çoklu klasörler için otomatik toplu içe aktarım mevcuttur. Veri dışa aktarımı ve çalma listeleri oluşturma da olanaklıdır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Передбачено можливість імпортування даних альбомів з gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon. Можливе автоматичне пакетне імпортування для декількох тек одночасно. Передбачено можливість експортування даних та створення списків відтворення.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxAlbum data can be imported from gnudb.org, MusicBrainz, Discogs, Amazon; automatic batch import is available for multiple folders. It is also possible to export data and generate play lists.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">可从 gnudb.org、MusicBrainz、Discogs 或 Amazon 上导入专辑数据，还支持自动多文件夹批量导入功能。您还可导出数据并生成播放列表。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">可以從 gnudb.org、MusicBrainz、Discogs、Amazon 匯入專輯資料；可以為多個資料夾進行自動批次匯入。也提供匯出資料與產生播放清單的功能。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default" width="1200" height="675">
      <image>https://kid3.kde.org/assets/img/screen169.png</image>
      <caption>Kid3 main window</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">النّافذة الرّئيسيّة لكِد3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Finestra principal del Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Finestra principal de Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Hlavní okno Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Kid3's hovedvindue</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Hauptfenster von Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Kid3 κύριο παράθυρο</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Kid3 main window</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Ĉefa fenestro de Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Ventana principal de Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Kid3 peaaken</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Kid3, leiho nagusia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Kid3:n pääikkuna</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Fenêtre principale de Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Jendela utama Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="is">Aðalgluggi Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Finestra principale di Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">Kid3 -ის მთავარი ფანჯარა</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">Kid3 주 창</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Hoofdvenster van Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Hovudvindauget i Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Główne okno Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Janela principal do Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Janela principal do Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Главное окно Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Hlavné okno Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Glavno okno Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Huvudfönstret i Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Kid3 ana penceresi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Головне вікно Kid3</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxKid3 main windowxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">Kid3 主窗口</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">Kid3 主視窗</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://kid3.kde.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kid3</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/index.php?application=kid3</url>
  <developer_name>Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ar">أورس فليش</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="cs">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="da">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="de">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="el">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="en-GB">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="eo">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="et">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="eu">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fi">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fr">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="id">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="is">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="it">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ka">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ko">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nn">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pl">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt-BR">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ru">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sk">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sl">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sv">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="tr">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="x-test">xxUrs Fleischxx</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="zh-CN">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="zh-TW">Urs Fleisch</developer_name>
  <update_contact>ufleisch_at_users.sourceforge.net</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">kid3</translation>
  <releases>
    <release version="3.9.4" date="2023-07-09">
      <description>
        <p>New</p>
        <ul>
          <li>All the official binaries are built with Qt 6. For macOS, the Darwin-amd64.dmg file is now the Qt 6 version, whereas systems older than Mojave need the package Darwin-Qt5.dmg. The string replacement settings stored by Qt 6 are not compatible with Qt 5 because a different encoding is used.</li>
          <li>Option "Select file on play" in "User Actions" settings tab.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Improved</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Click on play tool bar time toggles between elapsed and remaining time.</li>
          <li>The visibility and docked area of the play tool bar are restored.</li>
          <li>ID3v1: When setting multiple genres, use first supported element.</li>
          <li>Qt6: Use SVG icons for better performance in file list and dialog.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Fixed</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Do not mark all non-unified frames as modified if any non-unified frame is changed.</li>
          <li>Crash in Id3libMetadata when clicking Edit on unsupported frame.</li>
          <li>Setting text encoding on TXXX frames with TaglibMetadata.</li>
          <li>Skip non letter characters for first letter uppercase format.</li>
          <li>Discogs import: Fix values in Artist, Arranger and Performer frames, use "genres" if "styles" is empty, fetch correct cover art, support vinyl track numbers like A1.</li>
          <li>Qt6: Crash when adding item to config table.</li>
          <li>Qt6: Larger media player slider, do not repeat when last song has been played.</li>
          <li>Windows, TaglibMetadata: Support files larger than 2 GB.</li>
          <li>Windows, OggFlacMetadata: Build without libssp-0.dll.</li>
          <li>Windows, Mp4v2Metadata: Fix saving with file names containing non ASCII characters.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.9.3" date="2023-01-12"/>
    <release version="3.9.2" date="2022-08-06"/>
    <release version="3.9.1" date="2022-01-15"/>
    <release version="3.9.0" date="2021-12-18"/>
    <release version="3.8.7" date="2021-06-20"/>
    <release version="3.8.6" date="2021-03-18"/>
    <release version="3.8.5" date="2021-01-31"/>
    <release version="3.8.4" date="2020-09-26"/>
    <release version="3.8.3" date="2020-05-10"/>
    <release version="3.8.2" date="2020-01-23"/>
    <release version="3.8.1" date="2019-12-23"/>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
